

### PERSONAL DATA

- Ossastrasse 41, 12045, Berlin
- +49 1797296729
- ✓ kata.serfozo@gmail.com
- Be www.behance.net/kataserfozo
- nttps://kataserfozo.github.io

### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Photoshop	• • • • 0
Lightroom	
Illustrator	
InDesign	
Balsamique	
Sketch	
InVision	
AfterEffects	• 0 0 0 0
html, css	• • 0 0 0

### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Hungarian				
English				0
Swedish			0	0
German		0	0	0

#### **EXTRACURRICULAR**

- 6 months in New Zealand on a working holiday scheme
- 3 months experience as a barista in London
- Volunteering for 3 months in Portugal in a surf camp
- Working as a freelance photographer and weddings
- Experience in Studio Photography

#### **COURSES AND TRAININGS**

- Interaction Design specialization (Coursera)
- Certificates in Graphic Design,
   Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightroom and InDesign (Shawacademy, Udemy)

I'm a UI designer with a background in philology, finance, photography and graphic design. Due to my diverse professional experience I am able to adapt to different environments while adhering to professional integrity. Besides arts and creating, I love developing my skills, learning new tools and improving my design skillset, while making aesthetically pleasing and useful products and interfaces.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# 09/2018- 04/2019 UI Design course CareerFoundry

- UI design for music, messaging, note-taking applications
- UX and UI design for cooking application for mobile and responsive design
- UI design for delivery application for iOS and Android Native app
- UI design for money saving responsive website

# 10/2017 – 3/2018 Graphic and Web Design intern MediaSales, Budapest, Hungary

- · Creating banners, website and mobile interface design
- Creating images and ads for social media and presentations
- Designing products for print

## 04/2014 – 12/2016 Reporting Specialist British Telecom, Budapest, Hungary

- Designing and maitaining database of employees in Business Objects application
- Creating and running reports for management on employe utilisation rates on projects and project expenditures for forecasting pruposes
- Testing corporate data warehouse of the time, labour and project management tool
- Performing data cleanse and data analysis activities
- Controlling and updating labour rate card data

# 11/2013 - 03/2014 Finance Professional British Telecom, Budapest, Hungary

- Providing 1st Line Support for a Project and People Management System
- Performing system administration activities
- Explaining and looking for solutions for the users of the Management System

#### **EDUCATION**

09/2018 - 04/2019 CareerFoundry, distance education
 Ul Design

01/2010 - 06/2010 Rønde Højskole , Rønde, Denmark Arts, Project Management

© 09/2009 - 12/2013 Eötvös Loránd University, Budapest, Hungary BA, English and Scandinavian Studies